akiwood.com 2015-11-03

# 

**The Short Awesome Version:  **

Akiwood.com is an awesome website that does not steal or harvest any of your information.  The site is safe, and any place you are going to buy anything is secure.  The only way you will get on a mailing list from Akiwood.com is if you fill in one of the opt in forms.  If you want out, just unsubscribe at any time, there will always be a link at the bottom of the list emails for you to do that…

…In other words, there is never a reason to be a butt-hole and report spam over a list that YOU subscribed to. Simply click the unsubscribe button. 

Obviously, this is a for profit site that promotes home business opportunities and making money from home.  If you are one of those butt-monkeys that think everything is a pyramid scheme, I have 2 things to say to you:

  1. I feel sorry for you(and you need some education, [Click Here to get it](http://akiwood.com/grave-or-pyradmid/ "Enjoy"))
  2. You will probably enjoy another website more, so just leave now; thank you for stopping by!

If you want the full privacy policy, continue reading below, the [Disclaimer](http://akiwood.com/disclaimer/ "Disclaimer") is on another page.  We recommend that you buy everything we are selling because it just feels good to buy stuff.

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

1\. To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

2\. To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies.  We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.  Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Information Collected From All Visitors**

Visitors to this website who have javascript enabled are tracked using Google Analytics. Google Analytics collects the following types of information from users: Type of user agent (web browser) used, software manufacture and version number. Type of operating system Screen colors (color processing ability of the users screen) Javascript support Flash version Screen resolution Network location and IP address Can include country, city, state, region, county, or any other geographic data. Hostname Bandwidth (internet connection speed) Time of visit Pages visited Time spent on each page of the website Referring site statistics The website (URI) the user came through in order to arrive at this website (example: clicking on a hyperlink from Yahoo.com that took the user to this website) Search engine query used (example: typing in a phrase into a search engine like Google, and clicking on a link from that search engine) This data is primarily used to optimize our website for our visitors, however we will use this data for marketing purposes. An example of how this data could be used for marketing purposes would be to tell potential advertisers how many visitors we get to the website, where our visitors come from, and how they arrive at our website. This data DOES NOT include any personalized identification information such as: Names Phone Numbers Email Addresses Mailing Addresses Social Security Numbers Bank Account Numbers Credit Card Information

**DISCLAIMER**

We are a website that needs compensation to operate like any other website on the internet. We may receive consideration for our reviews but we are totally unbiased and do not accept paid reviews or fake reviews claiming to be something they are not.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on February 10, 2011

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

Administrator  
accounts@akiwood.com
